<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BD Division</string>
    <string name="division1">Dhaka Division is an administrative division within Bangladesh. Dhaka is the capital city of Bangladesh and also the largest city as well of the country. It comes among the 10 most populous cities of the world. The Division as constituted prior to 2015 covered an area of 31,051 km2,[2] and had a population of 47,424,418 at the 2011 Census. However, following the separation of the new Mymensingh Division in 2015, the area has been reduced to 20,508.8 km2 with a population at the 2011 Census of 36,433,505.
        Dhaka Division is bounded by Mymensingh Division to the north, Barisal Division to the south, Chittagong Division to the east and south-east, Sylhet Division to the north-east, Rangpur Division to the north-west, and Rajshahi Division to the west and Khulna Divisions to the south-west.</string>
    <string name="division2">Chittagong Division is geographically the largest of the eight administrative divisions of Bangladesh. It covers the south-easternmost areas of the country, with a total area of 33,771.18 km2 (13,039.13 sq mi) and a population at the 2011 census of 28,423,019. The administrative division includes mainland Chittagong District, neighbouring districts and the Chittagong Hill Tracts.
    </string>

    <string name="division3">Rajshahi Division is one of the eight first-level administrative divisions of Bangladesh. It has an area of 18,174.4 square kilometres (7,017.2 sq mi) and a population at the 2011 Census of 18,484,858.[3] Rajshahi Division consists of 8 districts, 70 Upazilas (the next lower administrative tier) and 1,092 Unions (the lowest administrative tier). This division is most valuable division of Bangladesh . It has an excellent rail and road communication infrastructure. The divisional capital of Rajshahi is only six-seven hours road journey away from Dhaka, the capital city.

Until 2010 this Division comprised 16 districts,but early in that year it was divided into two, when a new Division (Rangpur Division) was formed out of the 8 northerly districts that until then had been part of Rajshahi Division. Rajshahi was dominated by various Rajas, Maharajas and Zamindars.</string>
    <string name="division4">Sylhet Division is the northeastern division of Bangladesh. It is bordered by the Indian states of Meghalaya, Assam and Tripura to the north, east and south respectively, and by the Bangladeshi divisions of Chittagong to the southwest and Dhaka and Mymensingh to the wes</string>
    <string name="division5">Khulna Division is one of the eight divisions of Bangladesh. It has an area of 22,285 km2 (8,604 sq mi) and a population of 15,563,000 at the 2011 Census (preliminary returns). Its headquarters and largest city is Khulna city in Khulna District.</string>
    <string name="division6">Mymensingh Division is one of the eight administrative divisions of Bangladesh. It has an area of 10,485 square kilometres (4,048 sq mi) and a population of 11,370,000 as of the 2011 census. It was created in 2015 from districts previously composing the northern part of Dhaka Division. Its headquarters are in Mymensingh city in Mymensingh District.</string>
    <string name="division7">Rangpur Division is one the Divisions in Bangladesh. It was formed on 25 January 2010.The Rangpur division consists of eight districts. There are 58 Upazilas or subdistricts under these eight districts. Rangpur is the northernmost division of Bangladesh and has a population of 15,665,000 in the 2011 Census.</string>
    <string name="division8">Barisal Division is one of the eight administrative divisions of Bangladesh. Located in the south-central part of the country, it has an area of 13,644.85 km2 (5,268.31 sq mi), and a population of 8,325,666 at the 2011 Census. It is bounded by Dhaka Division on the north, the Bay of Bengal on the south</string>

</resources>